Come on friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel, we are going to talk about
how you will do accident insurance from the PhonePe application, so friends,
if any accident happens to you in the future, then
friends, if you do
accident insurance from the application on your phone,
then friends, you will get some
money here from the PhonePe application,
so friends, if you do
accident insurance here, then friends, what will
you have to do, so friends,
if you do not know how to do it, then friends, we are going to
tell you what you will have to do,
so friends,
what you will have to do first of all, you have to come back,
after coming back, now you have to open your Play Store in
this way, after opening,
now you will have to type PhonePe,
so friends, like you will click on PhonePe and
type, so friends, now
what you will have to do simply in your phone, in this way
you have to download the application on the phone,
after downloading, what you will have to do simply,
you have to click on Open,
like you will click on Open, so friends, now the
application on your phone will open in front of you in this way, so
friends, now what you will have to do is
come down  After coming down, now you will simply
get many options here, here bike car help and here
accident and here turn
type and you will get many options like this, so
friends what will you have to do
here, friends what will you have to do here, if
you want to get accident insurance,
then friends you have to
click on accident insurance,
click on the accident option, so friends, as
you will click on the accident option from here, then
friends, now the options will open in front of you in this
way, here
accident and soil and select here, here
five means ₹50000 Congress
here you can get 510 lakhs here you can get up to 20 lakhs,
but friends
how much will you have to pay here, 25 rupees 49
rupees ₹295 1000 99 means friends you will have to pay this much
and if you get
insurance done for 25 rupees here, then
friends you will get ₹50000 here,
if friends you get it done for 49 rupees
So friends, you will get ₹1 lakh here.
If you get it done for 249 here,
then friends you will get 5 lakh rupees. If
you get it done for 50049 from here,
then friends you will get 10 lakh rupees. If
you pay 1000 99 rupees from here,
then friends you will get 20 lakh rupees. So
friends, you can do any of these
features here. So
friends, what will we do
here, we will do the ₹2500 thing.
After doing this, you have to click on Get Policy. So
friends, as soon as you click on Get, then
friends, options will open in front of you in this way.
So friends,
which company is
giving you insurance here? Friends, Reliance is
giving you insurance here. So friends,
you can read its complete data by clicking on Verify.
Friends, which
company is giving you insurance? How much insurance are you getting
here? Then it is Reliance company which is
giving you accident insurance personally here. Here friends,
you are going to get two films and two benefits.
So friends  If you have
brought a car with you, that is, an accident happens, then only
friends, you will get money, you
can read everything here, after reading,
what will you have to do simply,
after coming, now what will you have to do simply,
now you have to enter your name here, so
friends, whatever name you have, you have to enter your name,
after entering, now you have to
enter Sapna's email ID,
after entering the email ID, now you have to click on the data, so
friends, now whatever data you have,
you have to fill in your data in this way,
after filling in the data, now
you have to accept the terms and conditions,
after accepting, you have to
click on this option, so friends, as you
click on this option,
friends, now the option to add a bank account will come in front of you in this way, so
friends,
you have to click on add bank,
after clicking, now what will you have to do simply,
you have to click on your bank,
friends, whatever bank you have,
you have to click on your bank, so friends, as soon as you
click on your bank, friends, your
bank account will be added in this way, it will be
linked here on donation
After clicking on Dum,
what you simply have to do is click on it,
after that your insurance will be
activated there, like if I
click on OK here, then friends, my
payment will be successful, so
friends, my insurance will be
activated here, so friends, in this way,
friends, your insurance is valid for one year,
if friends, after one year, if
you do not get it renewed, then friends,
your insurance will expire, that is, friends, if
you pay Rs 25, if friends,
if you have any problem within a year, then friends,
Reliance will
give you Rs 50,000 here because
you will get it only if you have insurance, if
friends, you do not have insurance, then
friends, you will not get Rs 50,000, if
friends, you pay Rs 5009 here, then
friends, you will get up to Rs 10 lakh, the
company will give you this, so friends, if
you want to get accident insurance, then
friends, you can get it done in this way, there will be no
problem, no problem,
so friends, see you in the next video, till then
Jai Hind Vande Mataram